解释下你的行为
Explain yourself.
我在拍你的脚给变态看
I'm taking photos of your feet for perverts.
-恶... -听我说完
- Ew! - Hear me out.
还记得你买的运动鞋没法退
Remember when you couldn't return those sneakers you bought
让我拿到网上卖吗
and asked me to sell them online?
我刚放到二手网站上
Right after I listed them...
就收到一条信息问我
...I got a message asking
鞋子有没有被穿过 有没有汗臭
if they'd been worn and sweat in.
我还没来得及说谎说没有
Before I could lie and say no...
就收到另一条信息
...I got another message.
"我可以看你的脚吗"
"Can I see your feet?"
原来网上有无数这样的恋足癖
Apparently, there are a ton of these feet freaks on the Internet.
天啊 这是你写的吗
Oh, my God, did you write this?
"我的小脚脚超爱出汗"
"My little piggies got so sweaty."
-很性感吧 -才不
- Sexy, right? - No.
一点也不 恶心死了
No, it's gross!
那双运动鞋可是卖到200刀哦
That pair of sneakers went for over $200.
我衣柜里还有很多鞋
I have more in my closet.
那一幕发生在三周前
That was three weeks ago,
打那以后我们卖鞋赚了好多钱
and we have made a ton of money since.
而我只需要每天穿不一样的鞋子
All I have to do is wear a different shoe every day.
各项标准都达标
Hitting all of the right notes...
寄出去吧
Ship it.
入围本届
Les finalistes
国际橱柜展览会决赛的选手有...
pour L'Expo Internationale du Closet sont...
柏林 康妮西橱柜
Kabinett Konig, Berlin.
普里契特橱柜
Pritchett's Closets --
太棒了
Hah! Yes!
太棒了太棒了
Yes, yes, yes!
太爽了
Yes!
你们太恶心了
You guys are so gross!
这是我公司史上首次
For the first time in company history,
去参加
we are going to
国际橱柜展览会
the Expo Internationale du Closet!
柏林
...Berlin.
普里契特橱柜
Pritchett's Closets.
我的亲娘啊 我们做到了
Son of a bitch, we did it!
我们做到了
We did it!
曼尼 我感谢你
Manny, I appreciate
从学校回来见证这一刻
you coming from college for this moment.
是啊
Yeah...
像这样的事
Something like this only happens
一周...一年...一辈子一遇吧
once in a wee-- year -- lifetime?
可不是嘛
If that!
我习惯了某些
I'm accustomed to certain creature comforts
在学校难以得到的物质享受
that are hard to come by at school,
所以我就常回家来...借点东西
so I've been stopping home to...borrow things.
看来我得去买东西了
You know, I may have to go shopping.
我的礼服尺寸都有点不太合适了
I'm kind of between tuxedos, size-wise, right now.
-所以这个...很了不起吗 -当然了
- Oh, so this is a... big deal? - It is.
但是 但不用觉得你也得做到这地步
But, uh, don't feel you have to live up to this.
因为这种压力能压垮一个孩子
because that kind of pressure can kill a kid.
可能是克莱尔给我打电话了
That's probably Claire calling me.
今天电话肯定要打爆了
These will be rolling in all day, you know.
喂
Hello?
现在谁还用传真机啊
Who still uses fax machines?
大家肯定想在办公室看到我
You know what? People are gonna want to see me at the office.
我先打半场高尔夫 再早点儿过去
I'll just play nine holes and head in early, huh?
-再见 孩子 -再见
- See you, kid! - See you.
我的新房地产公司
My new real-estate company
离第一笔买卖就差这么点
is this close to its first sale.
我们迫切需要一笔买卖
A sale we really need!
不只是为了证明我的老合伙人错了
Not just to prove my old partners wrong,
也是为了维持生计
but also to pay the bills.
不幸的是
Unfortunately,
我的客户突然临阵变卦
my client has developed a case of cold feet.
菲尔 这房子符合我的一切要求
Phil, this house is everything I have wanted.
太好了 我们要出个报价了吗
Great! Should we write up an offer?
但是 我感受到了一种敌意负能量
But, I am feeling a hostile energy.
我可以跟你保证
I can assure you --
这房子除了快乐的记忆没别的
this house is filled with nothing but happy memories.
-如果这些墙会说话的话 -它们会
- If these walls could talk... - They can.
而且正在说
And they are.
我个人是不相信
Personally, I don't believe in
什么邪灵巫术
any of that evil-spirit mumbo jumbo.
作为一个魔术师 我知道任何恐怖灵异
As a magician, I've learned that every spooky happening
都有一个完美的合理解释
has a perfectly reasonable explanation.
即便是最可怕的魔术 撒旦电梯
Even the eeriest of illusions, Satan's Elevator,
也只是利用了两面镜子和一个小...
is really just two mirrors and a tiny...
想得美
Nice try.
菲尔告诉我的时候
When Phil told me about this house,
我自愿帮助他
I offered to help.
现在曼尼上大学了
Now that Manny's away at college
乔也去上幼儿园了
and Joe goes to kindergarten,
我就有时间继续我原来的爱好之一
I have time for one of my old hobbies --
逼恶魔现出原形
confronting the devil in all his forms.
我需要的东西都带来了
I have everything I need --
鼠尾草 梵蒂冈的餐厅的勺子
sage, a spoon from the Vatican cafeteria,
我的沙球
my maracas --
她来了
Oh, here she is!
格拉哈姆太太 气色不错
Mrs. Graham, looking well!
今天的抗老化缩氨酸怎么样了
How are those peptides doing?
太好了 我的巫师帮我重新排列了它们
Ooh, terrific! My shaman realigned them.
我买到最后一个全味贝果
And I got the last everything bagel,
看来我们今天都有个不错的开始
so I guess we both got off to a great start today.
怎么样 买栋房子吧
What say, we buy a house?
这是歌洛莉亚
Oh, this is Gloria.
她会解决你的担心
She'll be addressing your concerns.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
我立马就对你产生信任了
I instantly trust you.
为什么呢
Why is that?
我知道了
Oh, I got it.
我们都曾经是猫
We were once cats together.
我开玩笑的啦 我才没那么神经
I joke! I'm not that crazy.
跟我说说这屋里的幽灵吧
Now, tell me about the ghost.
在这种郊区的房子里
Well, in these suburban cases,
一般都只是低级阴魂
it's usually a low-level haunting,
可能是一个被拖欠工资的死园丁
like a dead unpaid gardener,
或者是一位吃醋的死男友
a dead jealous boyfriend,
也可能是一条还有东西没叼回来的死狗
a dead dog who left something unfetched.
好了 进来吧
Okay. Here we go.
她对这种价位能就买到采光与通风
Oh, she's just taken with the natural light
这么好的房子感到震惊
and the flow at this price.
但是每次都还是会吓到我
It -- it still gets me every time.
你做到了 你个混蛋
You did it, you bastard!
欲变世界
Be the change
先变其身
you want to see in the world --
我已经尽快赶过来了
I got here as soon as I could!
在某种程度上 甘地说过的话
In some ways, the words of Gandhi
在今天比过去更真切
are truer today than ever before.
全世界都开始注意到极光超大衣柜了
The world is taking notice of the Aurora walk-in,
它模糊了收纳和避难所之间的界限
which is blurring the line between storage and sanctuary.
我想要说几句来赞美我们的基石
I want to take a moment to celebrate our rock,
这一切的基础
our foundation,
一个我们亏欠了很多的人
someone to whom we owe a very special debt...
乔茜
Josie.
基石 基础 乔茜
Rock? Foundation? Josie?
那丫是谁啊
Who is that?!
为了感谢大家的杰出成果
And to thank you all for your amazing accomplishments,
今天下午我请大家吃冰淇淋
I have got an ice-cream cart coming in this afternoon!
没错
That's right.
IT男 我需要你帮个忙
I.T. Guy, I need your help.
-雪茄烟灰又掉到键盘里了 -比那重要
- Cigar ash in your keyboard again? - Something bigger.
但你还是把小吸尘器带上吧
But, yeah, bring that little vacuum.
我姐姐帕姆来我们这暂住几周
My sister Pam came to stay with us for a couple weeks.
一年前就来了
A year ago.
住在楼上那套房里
In the unit upstairs --
那里以前是出租来赚钱的
which we used to rent for money,
我们需要那些钱
which we need
来养活楼下这套房里的人
to pay for everybody in the unit downstairs.
我们别无选择
We had no choice.
她当时怀孕了
She was pregnant.
但孩他爸 博 进监狱了
The father, Bo, was in jail,
而且她还是我最好的朋友
and she happens to be my best friend.
是啊 你们的友谊像卡通里的猫和老鼠一样
Yeah, yeah, like Tom and Jerry are best friends.
帕姆 你有记得买橙子吗
Pam, did you remember the oranges?
你敢再说一次"橙子"试试
Say "oranges" one more time.
橙子
Oranges.
-再说一次试试 -橙子 橙子
- Say it one more time! - Oranges! Oranges!
她还不关好门
And then she left the door open,
可怜的拉里跑了出去和一只负鼠打了一架
and poor Larry got out and got in a fight with a possum.
现在我们不得不每天中午给它喂抗生素
Now we have to give him antibiotics every day at noon,
它特别不愿意吃
which he hates.
但好的一面是
On the positive side,
我们两个每天中午都回家吃午餐
we've both been coming home at lunch
因为这活得俩人干
because it's a two-man job,
我们每天午休时享受的另一件事
as it what we've also been enjoying
也要俩人一起"干"
on our little lunch break...
你穿这身正装真好看
You look really cute in that suit.
你穿这条运动短裤真好看
You look really cute in those gym shorts.
猫咪还得再吃八天的抗生素
Only eight more days of cat antibiotics.
你敢再说一次"抗生素"试试
Say "nntibiotics" one more time.
抗生素
Antibiotics.
好的 亲爱的 但帕姆的亲子课
Okay, sweetie, but Pam's Mommy and Me class
一小时就结束了 你可得快点回来
is only an hour, so, you know, hurry.
有惊喜吗
Oh, a surprise, huh?
那好 我等不急了
Okay. Okay, well I can't wait.
哪位
Yeah?
下午好
Afternoon.
我的天 你就是那个惊喜
Oh, my God, are you the surprise?
我还以为是蜡烛或铺满鲜花的床那类的
I was thinking candles, or flowers on the bed --
我叫博·约翰逊
My name is Bo Johnson,
我来见我的宝贝儿子
and I am here to meet my baby boy
赢回我的一生挚爱
and win back the love of my life,
帕姆·塔克女士
Miss Pam Tucker.
天哪 你就是 你就是博
Oh, my -- You're-you're B- you are Bo.
好吧 帕姆不在家
Um, okay, well, Pam is not here.
我是米奇尔 卡梅隆的丈夫
I'm Mitchell, Cameron's husband.
他说过很多你的事
He's talked so much about you.
他过去在高中时
Oh, well, he did have a little thing for me
-的确有点迷恋我 -是啊
- back in high school. ?- Yeah.
看来他只喜欢咱们这类型的
I guess he's got a type.
别闹了 别闹了
Stop it! Stop it.
-我哪能和你比 -如果你不介意的话
- I am nothing like -- - Well, if you don't mind, actually,
我想先进门
I'd like to come in?
我得去马厩看看状况
I got to see man about a horse.
可我们这没有...
But we don't have --
那是种婉转的说法
That's a classy way of saying
是我要去释放一下膀胱的意思
I got to make my bladder gladder.
卫生间 好的
Bathroom! Uh, yes...
在走廊尽头 右手边
Uh, end of the hall on -- on the right. Yep.
那些青少年时尚杂志是我们女儿的
Oh, and the Teen Vogues are our daughter's!
我们根本不知道黛米·洛瓦托是谁
We don't even know who Demi Lovato is!
好吧 拉里怎么又跑出去了
Okay, how did Larry get out again?
天啊 肯定是你姐
God, it must've been your sister.
你猜谁在卫生间里
So, guess who is in the bathroom.
我的惊喜不过是蜡烛而已
Oh, well, my surprise was just candles,
但我也来者不拒
but I'm not saying no.
不 是博
No, uh... It's Bo.
-我的博 -不
- My Bo? - No --
应该说是帕姆的博
Well, technically, he's-he's more Pam's Bo,
而我是你的米奇尔
and I am your Mitchell.
但是的 他来接帕姆和宝宝回家
But yes. Yeah, he's here to take Pam and the baby home!
这是多好的事啊
I mean, how great is that?
卡梅隆·塔克
Cameron Tucker!
从我家里滚出去
Get the hell out of my house.
合上你的双臂
Close those arms.
别这样 小卡
Come on, Cam.
-是啊 别这样 小卡 -不
- Yeah, come on, Cam. - No.
我不准你接近我姐姐
You are not getting anywhere near my sister.
快滚
Now get out!
快点 快滚
Let's go! Get out!
那他就会改成在门口等帕姆啊
Uh, won't he just wait for Pam outside?
-因为 -好吧 给我回来
- I mean -- - Okay, you know... Come back in!
太好了 拉里又跑出去了
Great. There goes Larry again.
我开始认为它不愿意在咱家待着了
You know, I'm starting to think he's unhappy living here.
很好 很好
Good. Good.
有魔术贴的鞋不行
Uh, no Velcro.
我们的品牌要更高级些
Our brand is a little more upscale.
又一个买家看同一双脚看腻了
Another buyer is tired of seeing the same feet.
这成了我的错吗
Oh, it's my fault now?
他也没为保持新鲜感做出什么贡献啊
What's he doing to keep things interesting?
我为什么在乎
Why do I care?
真没想到你愿意这么做
I'm surprised you were open to this.
真没想到你这么熟练
I'm surprised you know how to do this.
别忘了
Don't forget,
我们一会得去老妈公司把鞋发出去
we have to get over to mom's work to ship shoes later.
等一下 你一直在用老妈的快递吗
Wait a second, you're using Mom's FedEx?
每次她和老爸晚上出去奢侈
Every time she and Dad have a fancy night out,
她总会用"卢克的大学基金"
she uses the hashtag "Luke's college fund."
所以我也占占她的便宜
So, yeah, I'm using her account.
你是不是有瞒着一些关于这房子的事
Is there something you're not telling me about this house?
我有点感觉到了凶杀案的气息
I am kind of getting a murdery vibe.
唯一与这幢房子有关的"杀"
The only killing that's ever gonna happen in this house
是你哪天转卖时 会杀光买家的钱包
is the one that's gonna happen when you sell the place.
笑声会激怒鬼魂们 菲尔
Laughter makes the spirits hungry, Phil!
鬼魂们
Spirits?
有不止一个的意思吗
You means there's more than one?
吉尔
Hi, Gil.
等等 不 吉尔
Wait. No. Gil?
歌洛
Hey, Glo?
你能来我真的很高兴
Uh, super stoked you're here.
希望你能听我一个小建议
If-if I could give you one tiny note?
格拉哈姆太太的害怕等级
Mrs. Graham's terror level,
我们需要把它往下降
which should be going down,
-但目前在升高 -我的也在升高
- is actually going up. - Mine too.
事实上我已经慌了
Actually, I'm panicking right now!
你不会相信我现在所感受到的
You can't believe what I'm sensing right now!
这里有嗡嗡声 震动 恐惧
There is like, a humming sound, vibrations, fear!
我很肯定那都是我发出来的
I'm pretty sure that's all coming off of me,
因为我很需要的这桩生意要黄了
because I'm about to lose a sale I really need.
这样如何 你稍微包装一下
How about this? Just-just spin it a little.
你想让我做什么
What are you asking me to do?
在房地产界 没有烂房
In real estate, there are no dumps.
只有待修房
There are fixer-uppers.
面积小就说很温馨
A small house is cozy.
我们又不知道这个灵体是坏的
How do we know this presence is bad?
比如《鬼马小精灵》或圣灵
What about Casper? Or the Holy Ghost?
人们特喜欢那种的
People love those guys --
菲尔
Phil.
情况很糟 是不是
It's bad, isn't it?
不 情况其实很好
No, it's-it's actually really good.
歌洛莉亚正告诉我她有了很大进展
Gloria was just saying she's making real progress.
-对吧 歌洛莉亚 -抱歉
- Right, Gloria? - I'm sorry,
这幢房子里有很令人不安的灵体
but there is a disturbing presence in this house
我觉得我也驱逐不了
that I don't think that I can drive out.
那我肯定不买了
Well, that is it for me.
菲尔 如果你有不闹鬼
Phil, please let me know
而且也离我的灵媒很近的房子
if you find something less haunted,
请你一定要告诉我
still within walking distance to my psychic.
我们马上回来
We'll be right back.
博 你想喝冰茶吗
Bo, you want some iced tea?
那太好了 谢谢
That'd be great. Thank you.
不 不准给他冰茶喝
No, you are not giving him iced tea.
这可不是花园派对
This is not a garden party.
但他大老远来弥补错误
But he did come all this way to make things right.
你知道吗 小卡
And you know what, Cam?
监狱是会改变人的
Prison changes people.
-是吗 -总是往好了改
- Oh, does it? - Always in a good
永久性的改变
and permanent way.
看看他啊
I mean, look at him...
不 不要看他
No. Do not look at him.
他就是个男妖
He is a siren.
他用那双美丽的大蓝眼勾引你
He draws you in with those big beautiful blue eyes,
等你反应过来 你已经
and the next thing you know, you're giving him
把你曾祖父内战时期的刺刀给他了
your great-grandfather's Civil War bayonet
而他拿去卖了买魔豆
and he's selling it for Magic Beans.
魔豆是他喝的威士忌牌子
It's the brand of whiskey he drinks.
我认为该给他第二次机会
I just -- I think he deserves a second chance.
你为什么突然在意起
Why do you suddenly care so much
帕姆和博能不能复合
if Pam and Bo are back together?
我是个离婚律师 小卡
I'm a divorce lawyer, Cam.
我总能看到家庭四分五裂
I see families torn apart all the time.
人的感情那么受伤代价太高了
The emotional cost is just too high.
一切的代价都太高太贵了
The cost of everything is too high!
帕姆自己铺了床
Look, Pam made her bed.
现在需要她从床上下来
Now she needs to get out of it
我才能把床垫翻一下接着赚钱
so I can flip the mattress to make some money off of it.
我没想到听起来会这么像皮条客
Sounded more pimpy than I intended.
或许帕姆不想在楼上住下去了
Maybe Pam doesn't want to live upstairs anymore.
或许她想跟他回密苏里
Maybe she wants to go with him to Missouri.
又或许是你不想让帕姆在楼上住下去了
Or maybe you don't want Pam to live upstairs
是你想让她跟他回密苏里
and you want her to go home to Missouri.
我不小心听到你们说话
I couldn't help but overhear,
因为我们就在同一间房间里
since we're practically in the same room
你们说话又很大声
and you ain't exactly whispering...
我能替自己说几句话吗
Can I say something on my behalf?
不 不能
No, you may not!
因为如果你在乎我姐姐
Because if you cared about my sister,
小卡尔霍恩出生时你就会在这
you would've been here the moment baby Calhoun was born!
我知道 但在我因为
I know, but when I got out of jail
打了警马服刑出狱后
for punching that police horse,
我发现我的卡车被拖走了
I discovered my truck had been towed.
我不得不卖血浆换现金
I had to sell my plasma for cash.
他会替别人着想 多高尚
He thinks of others. Very noble.
我只听到了没车又没钱
All I'm hearing is no car, no money,
免疫系统低下
compromised immune system.
这模样真值得我们学习
What a great role model.
是的 他模样的确不错
And yes, he could be a model,
但我是不会被那对美丽的蓝眼睛蛊惑的
but I will not be distracted by those beautiful big blue eyes.
小卡 我都懂
Cam, I get it, all right?
我犯过很多错
I made a lot of mistakes.
但就像我的血液一样
But like my plasma,
我要贯彻积极的B型阳性
I decided to "B-positive."
我搭车 我打奇怪的零工
I hitchhiked, I took odd jobs,
为了到这来能做的我都做了
whatever I could do to get here.
帕姆 我们的孩子卡尔霍恩
I mean, Pam, our boy Calhoun,
他们是我的家人
they're my family.
你也是我的家人
Hell, you're my family.
我很想相信你 博
Okay, I want to believe you, Bo,
但我...
but, yeah, I just --
我被伤过太多次了
yeah, I've been burned too many times.
说到伤 我有样东西想给你看看
About that... I got something to show you.
塔克 石墙杰克逊将军
Old Stonewall Tucker
会希望这东西能物归原主的
would've wanted you to have this back.
石墙将军
Stonewall.
希望不是从人家雕像手里偷的
I'm guessing his statue's no longer in the park.
-你不是卖了吗 -那是过去的博
- I thought you sold this. - Welp, that was the old Bo.
全新的博攒钱买回来还给你
The new Bo saved up and bought it back for you.
-你瞧 -相信我
- See? - Believe me,
我只想弥补过错
I'm trying to do the right thing.
博
Bo...
他怎么会在这
What the hell is he doing here?!
帕梅隆
Now, Pameron,
博是来重新争取你和小卡尔霍恩的
Bo came back for you and baby Calhoun!
是的 给他个机会好吗
Yeah, just-just give him a chance, okay?
我的天
Oh, my gosh.
就是他吗
Is this him?
那是我儿子吗
Is-is that my boy?
不 这是我的车 我有个迷你小司机
No. This is my car and I have a little tiny driver.
当然是他
Of course it's him!
你别靠近我们
You stay away from us,
-博勒加德·拉维恩·约翰逊 -拜托
- Beauregard Lavern Johnson! - Come on --
也别再用你致命的蓝眼睛视奸我
And stop undressing me with your devil blue eyes!
这样吧 我去
Okay, You know what? I'll-I'll go --
我去和她谈谈
I'll go talk to her.
谢谢你刚才在小卡面前维护我
Hey, thank you for pleading my case back there with Cam.
我看得出来你是个好律师
I can tell, you're good lawyer.
我也看得出来你是个好人
And I can tell you are a good man.
我会一直支持你的
I am team Bo all the way.
那太好了
All right, good.
因为我可能需要一些法律建议
'Cause I-I might need some legal counsel.
那个刺刀不是我买回来的
See, I-I didn't buy that bayonet back,
是我偷回来的
so much as I stole it.
天啊
Oh, dear.
大家 打扰一下
Excuse me, everyone!
作为创始人
As founder of this company,
我用血泪独自创立了这间公司
which I built with my own sweat and tears,
我想简单说几句
I'd like to say a few words.
在迈进未来前
Before going into the future,
向我们的过去致敬是很重要的
it's important we honor how we got here.
所以我做了个小短片
So I put together a little presentation.
爸 我们在吃冰激凌
Dad, we're having ice cream.
他们可以边舔边看
They can lick and watch.
马尾男 关灯
Ponytail, lights.
一幅横贯欧洲的铁幕正在落下
An iron curtain was descending over Europe.
但在俄亥俄州的杨斯顿市 一个孩子诞生了
But in Youngstown, Ohio, a child is born.
虽然少年时期的杰·普里契特是个明星球员
While young Jay Pritchett was superstar athlete,
但他还是个艺术家
he was also an artist
梦想要为某个业界带来革命性变化
who dreamed of revolutionizing an industry --
衣柜业
closets.
他就是不能让我当一天主角
He just couldn't let me have my day.
非得喧宾夺主
He had to make it all about him.
真是太恶心了
It was disgusting.
不过...
Although...
他扮演自己父亲
the scene of him playing his father
拒绝借他创业资金的那一幕
denying him a startup loan?
出人意料地动人心弦
Surprisingly powerful.
当全美忙着跳哈娑舞时
While America was doing the Hustle,
杰也在"舞"力全开要建起商业帝国
Jay as hustling to build an empire,
这就是为什么有家报纸称他为
which is why one newspaper called him
"柜界最努力之人"
"The hardest working man in closets."
那是他自己打的广告
That was an ad.
谁能料想到这家
Who would've thought the company,
由那个男孩建起的公司
built by that little boy,
有一天也能在
would one day be the toast
国际衣柜界里成为业界楷模
of the international closet world?
恭喜大家 我们做到了
Congratulations. We did it.
玛格丽特调了一些酒
Margaret's mixing some drinks.
下午愉快
Enjoy the afternoon.
-赞啊 -谢谢
-Nice! -Thank you.
格拉哈姆太太马上要走了
Okay, Mrs. Graham's car is on its way!
你只剩五分钟时间说服她
You have five minutes to convince her
这房子没问题
that this house is fine!
有东西在这墙里 菲尔
Something's in this wall, Phil.
不 我已经听够这些鬼话了
No, I am done with this nonsense!
真不敢相信这话居然
I can't believe I'm hearing this
出自一个相信魔术[法]的人之口
from a person that believes in magic!
以后我不会承认我说过这话
I'm not the one who told you this,
但魔术不是魔法
but magic isn't actually magic.
这不是真从你耳里拿出来的
That didn't come from your ear.
什么 怎么可能
What? How?
你也是他们的一员
You're with them.
哪有什么"他们"啊 歌洛莉亚
There is no "them," Gloria.
所有人对这个戏法都会说"什么 怎么可能"
Everybody says "What? How?" to that trick.
这就是魔术的原理
That's how magic works.
一些看起来超自然的事情
Things that seem supernatural
其实都有非常合理的解释
actually have a perfectly logical explanation.
这面墙是热的 菲尔
This wall is warm, Phil.
正在散发出邪能
It's radiating evil.
才没有散发出什么邪...
It is not radiating evil --
的确是热的耶
Oh, that is warm.
这又是怎么回事
What was that?
-电路不行吗 菲尔 -你好大胆子
- Faulty wiring, Phil?! - How dare you.
我才不会卖别人电路不行的房子呢
I would never sell a house with faulty wiring!
你也能听到对吧
You can hear that, right?
你惹他们生气了
You made them angry.
我才不信这一套
I don't believe in any of this!
以防万一...
But just in case...
-这是什么 圣水吗 -不是
- What is this? Holy water? - ?No.
黄瓜水
Cucumber water.
你以为我这好皮肤是凭空来的吗
You think this skin just happens?
好... 好吧
Okay...okay.
卖家很快要回家了
The sellers are on their way home.
我们就把东西物归原位
Let's just put everything back the way we found it
然后顺路去个教堂吧
and maybe swing by a church.
挂上啊
Come on!
天啊
Oh, my God!
有蜜蜂
Bees! ?
快跑快跑快跑啊
Oh! Go! Go, go, go, go, go, go!
好消息 格拉哈姆太太 原来只是蜜蜂
Good news, Mrs. Graham, it's only bees!
我会再跟进公证行的文件
I'll follow up with the escrow documents!
恭喜你了
Congrats! Ow!
很有意思的小电影啊 老爸
So, that was a fun movie, Dad.
虽然有一点喧宾夺主了
Kind of made it all about you, though.
瞎说 来一杯杰丁尼
Nonsense. Try a Jay-tini.
不用了
I'm good.
恭喜参展 老板
Congratulations on the Expo, boss.
-谢谢 -谢谢
- Thanks. - Thanks.
我觉得那不知道啥名的女人是在对我说
I think that what's her name was talking to me.
是吗
Oh?
玛格丽特 我的孩子来这里做什么
Oh, Margaret, what are my kids doing here?
这些孩子来用我们公司的货运
Oh, the kids have been using the company shipping.
已经好几周了
They've been coming in for weeks.
我好醉啊
I am so drunk.
我是不是在大声吼
Am I screaming?
你们俩个在搞什么鬼
What do you two think you're doing?
我们俩就是来恭喜你们
We just came to congratulate you
刚发生的那件事
on that thing that happened.
-再给你们一次机会 -好吧
- Try again. - Fine.
但这件事怎么说都有点怪
But there's no nice way to say this.
我开始了一家公司
I started a company
专门把艾丽克斯那些恶心臭烘烘的原味鞋
selling Alex's disgusting, smelly shoes
卖给恋足变态们
to feet freaks.
这也太恶心了吧
Wow, that is so gross!
是很有胆识
More like gutsy.
要想白手起家一家公司
You got to get your hands dirty
就要能不怕苦不怕累不怕脏
to build a company from the ground up.
我为你感到骄傲 卢克
I'm proud of you, Luke.
等等
Uh, hold on.
是我想到去旧货店买鞋
It was my idea to start buying thrift-store shoes.
我扩大业务 还让利润加倍
I expanded the business and doubled our profits.
你看到艾丽克斯做的了吗
You see what Alex did?
她让业务增长
She grew the business.
把生意带到了更高的境界
She took it to the next level.
她做到了卢克尝试了许多年
She was able to achieve what Luke couldn't
但一直都做不到的事
despite years of trying.
其实也才几...
It's really only been a few --
没有根 你怎么成长
You can't grow what doesn't exist!
他们是在吵他们的事情了
Okay. Well, they're on their thing now.
我们赶紧走人
Just walk away.
你知道我陪伴了这公司多久吗
Do you know how long I've been with this company?
美国换了7任总统
Seven presidents.
还有4任教皇 是的 我看了你那电影
And four popes. Yes, Dad, I saw the movie.
你就不能让我今天威风一天吗
Couldn't you just let me have today?
-你为什么没打给我 -你说什么呢
- Why didn't you call me? - What are you talking about?
今天早上 当你听到这大消息时
This morning. When you got the big news.
我现在已经不是这公司的一部分了吗
I mean, am I not a part of this anymore?
现在是这情况了吗
Is that what's going on here?
我没打给你
I didn't call you
是因为我在等着你打给我祝贺我
because I was waiting for you to call me and say,
"恭喜啊 你成功了 乖女儿"
"Congratulations, you did it, honey."
结果我却得来这里
Instead, I had to come here
看一部"杰拉伯的劳伦斯"
and watch "Lawrence of A-Jay-bia."
-不然大家怎么会记得我的存在 -什么
- How else would anybody know I even existed? - What?
我整个职业生涯都在努力打进那展览会
I spent my entire career trying to get in the Expo,
你接掌公司两年内就做到了
and you come in and get it done in 2 years.
别这样 不用说也知道
Come on, it goes without saying
这间公司是因为有你才有今天
that this company would be nothing without you.
不 不知道
No, it doesn't.
-我就要听到你说出来 -你认真的吗
- Let me hear you say it. - Seriously?
是的 我要听
Yes. I want to hear it.
爸 如果不是你
Dad, if it weren't for you,
我们也不会有今天的成就
we wouldn't be where we are today.
您所有的辛勤付出
All of your hard work
为我们今日的成功打下了夯实的基础
laid the foundation for our success.
换你了
Now you.
如果我这么说 会显得太自大
Well, if I say it, it'll sound a little conceited.
不是让你说自己 是说我
No, not about you! About me!
你...
It's...
达成了这令人难以置信的成就
an unbelievable accomplishment.
你大大地超过我的期望
You've exceeded all my expectations,
而我的期望本来已经设得非常高了
which were ridiculously high to begin with.
公司找不到比你更好的接班人了
The company could not be in better hands.
谢谢你 爸爸
Thanks, Dad.
好吧 我们就先假设
Okay, let's just agree
你的出发点是好的
that your heart was in the right place
就是你还小卡刺刀这件事
giving Cam back his bayonet.
但像你这样的体面人...
But knowing what a decent person you are,
我确定你一定有计划要...
I'm sure you're planning on --
博 开门
Bo, open this door!
博
Bo!
Bo --
你是打算让我在车里等你多久啊
How long you expect me to wait out there in the car?
天啊 求你告诉我她是你的出租车司机
Oh, God, please tell me this is your cab driver.
我叫海瑟
I'm Heather.
就像海色 不过我是"瑟"
It's like feather, but with an "H".
我认识你这名字
I'm familiar with the name.
亲爱的 我很快就出来
Uh, I'll be right out, sweetie.
先等我跟客户聊完就行
I'm just finishing up with my client.
好的 品克先生 您就等着
Okay, Mr. Pringle, you can expect delivery
一公与一母南美栗鼠送到您府上
of one male and one female chinchilla
只需等...
in the next...
好险 她走了
Phew. Good. She's gone.
你能相信我是随机应变 现场编的吗
Can you believe I just thought of that on the spot?
我不要下楼 小卡
I'm not going down there, Cam.
我一到他身边就不清醒
I don't trust myself around him.
我看到他的脸庞 他的声音
I see that face, I hear that voice,
我的心就融化
I go all gooey.
这话你的同性恋友人十分赞同
You're preaching to the gay man's choir, here.
但你得为自己做决定
But you have to decide for yourself,
而且你得保持清醒
and you need to keep a clear head.
要不这样吧
You know what? All right.
教你一招我当年
So, here's a trick that I used
青春期情窦初开时用的招数
when I was coming of age.
我当时有一点缺乏自制力
So, I had a little bit of a self-control problem,
我会在我的手腕上绑一个橡皮筋
and I would put a rubber band around my wrist
每当我有冲动想要...
and flick it every time I got the urge
我就会弹一下
to...flick it.
以前我们一起看有型男的电视剧
You used to snap one of those like crazy
《正义前锋》时 你总疯狂弹啊
whenever we watched "Dukes of Hazzard."
是啊 所以我平安看完7季
Yeah. I got through all seven seasons --
一次特殊"事故"都没发生
zero incidents.
好了
Okay.
想说什么说吧
Say your piece.
但我先告诉你
But I'll tell you right now,
我可不会轻易被你说服
I ain't gonna make it easy for you.
你看起来真美啊 小帕姆
You sure look pretty, Pam'n'cheese.
博
Oh, Bo...
过来抱抱
Come here.
我们促成了这一对
We did that.
是啊 是我们促成的
Yeah. Yeah, we did.
我知道我配不上你
I know I don't deserve you,
但如果你与卡尔愿意要我
but if you and Cal will have me,
我发誓我愿意用我的余生
I promise to spend every day of my life
向你证明我值得托付
proving that I am worthy.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
看看这戒指真是太美了
Look at this beautiful ring!
简直太完美...
It's just so perfect --
谁是海瑟
Who's Heather?
这是卖我戒指的珠宝商的名字
Oh, that's the name of the jeweler I bought it from.
海瑟戒指与其他东西店
Heather's Rings and... things.
够了 不行 不可以
Okay! Nope! Mnh-mnh! Nope!
不行 连我都没办法再为你开脱了
No, even I can't spin this anymore.
听我说 博就是个烂人
All right. Bo is a disaster, okay?
他一点都没变
He -- he hasn't changed one bit.
他就是个骗子 还是个贼
He is a liar, he is a thief,
他白天就开始喝酒 他...
he is a day drinker, he --
他从海瑟那里偷来的这戒指
He stole that ring from Heather,
而海瑟人正在外面 以防你拒绝了博
who's waiting outside for him in case you say no.
你怎么能说出这些话
Hey! You can't say any of that!
我们有律师客户保密权
That's attorney-client privilege!
他还是个傻逼
He's also an idiot.
来 我才不会让你跟卡尔
Look, okay, I am not letting you and Cal
接近这烂人一步呢 好吗
go anywhere near him, all right?
真不敢相信我居然
I cannot believe I got drawn in
又被你大而深邃的蓝眼珠给迷惑了
by those big beautiful blue eyes again.
滚出我家
Get out of my house.
这你说了不算吧 是吧
Well, it's not really up to you, now is it?
你觉得呢 帕姆美人
What you think, Pamburger?
我...
Well, I --
滚出去
Get the hell out!
行
Fine.
还好我有善待海瑟 为她留着空调
I'm glad I left the air conditioning on for Heather.
我还...
I even got --
谢谢你了 米奇尔
Thanks, Mitchell...
谢谢你那样为我着想
...for taking care of me like that.
你在这里也有个家
You have a home here
-你在这里待多久都行 -米奇尔
- as long as you need it, okay? - Aww, Mitchell,
你真的有在为她着想
you really are looking out for my sister.
听我说 帕姆
And you know what, Pam?
既然你还会在这里多住一段时间
As long as you're gonna be staying here for a little while,
你要多注意随手关门啊
you got to mind the door a little better.
拉里老是会溜出去
Larry keeps getting out.
-你再说一次"拉里"试试 -行
- Say "Larry" one more time. - Okay.
拉里
Larry.
你妈打电话跟你说要播我的电影啦
Your mother called you about the screening of my film.
她放我们鸽子了
She blew us off,
用被蜜蜂攻击了的烂理由
some lame excuse about being attacked by bees.
管她的 我们开始看吧
Oh what the hell, let's start.
你在那里干嘛
What are you doing over there?
你才在里面干嘛吧
What are you doing up there?
那是你跟前第一夫人小瓢虫·约翰逊吗
Is that you with Lady Bird Johnson?
是啊 我可是当年衣柜杂志的
Sure is. I was Closet Magazine's
"业界不可错过新星"
"Movers and Groovers to Watch."
她做的介绍演说
She did the keynote,
还称赞了我的小胡子
complimented my mustache...
大好时光啊
Heady times.
那个新闻片段是怎么回事
What's with all that news footage?
历史背景也是很重要的
Well, historical context is important.
政府水门事件丑闻过后
Post-Watergate,
大众想要透明化
people wanted transparency,
所以设计了玻璃衣柜
hence the glass closet.
我跟你解释下为什么下一个镜头我没穿衣服
Now, let me explain why my shirt is off in the next shot.